nowinstock.net 2019-05-07

# Legal Information - NowInStock.net

_Last Updated: 2018-05-23_

## **_NowInStock.net Cookie Policy_**

NowInStock.net uses cookies, pixels and other technologies (collectively, "cookies") to provide you with essential tools and services, for example:

  * We use cookies to determine your user session.
  * Determine what trackers you would like to alerted on without creating an account.
  * Collect consent.
  * Third parties may also use cookies when you interact with NowInStock.net services. Those third parties can include search engines, providers of measurement and analytical services, social networks and advertising companies. Third parties use cookies in the process to provide content, including ads relevant to your interests, to measure the effectiveness of ads and to provide services on behalf of NowInStock.net.
  * Allow for affiliate advertising commissions to be attributed to NowInStock.net in turn keeping this site free for our users and visitors.

If you choose to block cookies from NowInStock.net, certain features will not work.

## **_NowInStock.net Privacy Policy_**

NowInStock.net has drafted this document, which details how we gather and disseminate information, in an effort to demonstrate our commitment to online privacy. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy.

### Full Commercial Disclosure

NowInStock.net is partnered with most retailers tracked on this site via affiliate programs. As a result, our site contains affiliate links to aid in funding the site. This is NOT an endorsement of these retailers.

### Use of Data

NowInStock.net uses data (email addresses or phone numbers) to send alerts to you our users. We do not monitor your site usage other than for web analytics or the storage of user and account preferences. However, our partners/affiliate advertisers can trap data in order for us to receive our commission for sales. Below we have broken out the different types of user data tracking systems which you may encounter by visiting the pages of NowInStock.net:

  * **Direct - NowInStock.net:**
    * **User Data** \- If you want alerts, signing up with an email address is mandatory. For text alerts, we need to store your phone number so we can text message you directly. IP addresses can also be stored. Lastly, we also store the items for which you subscribe to for alerting. We NEVER share your data with anyone, ever, PERIOD.
    * **Marketing** \- periodically we send email alerts which we feel are relevant to you based on your subscribed items. For example, if we add a new item that is not in your subscription list, we will email to let you know a new item has been added to our system which you might want to add to your account for alerting. We may also send newsletters as well.
  * **Analytics** : 
    * **Google Analytics** \- this is the web analytics service which NowInStock.net uses to monitor visitors to our site and how users interact with NowInStock.net. To learn more about Google Analytics privacy, please visit: [https://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html)
  * **Social Widgets** : 
    * **Facebook** \- "Like Button" is used to allow for easy liking of our pages. To review the Facebook privacy policy, please visit: <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>
    * **Twitter** \- "Twitter Button" is used on NowInStock.net to allow for easy 'tweeting' of pages on our site. To see Twitter's privacy policy please visit: <https://twitter.com/privacy>
    * **Google+** \- "+1 Button" is used to allow easy sharing of pages on our site with your Google+ account. To review the Google+ privacy policy, please visit: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>
    * **DISQUS** \- is used for our commenting system that allows users to interact with one another. This system provides an invaluable resource to users whenever items are extremely hard-to-find. DISQUS does implement display advertising to support their platform. For more information on DISQUS, please visit: <https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy>
  * **Site Search** : 
    * **Google Custom Search** \- We use Google Custom Search to index and allow our site to be searched by you the users. You can review the Google Privacy policy for more. <https://policies.google.com/privacy>
  * **Display Advertising:**
    * NowInStock.net is partnered with several display advertisers. Below is the current list of advertisers we are partnered with: 
  * **Affiliate Advertising:**
    * NowInStock.net is partnered with several advertisers via affiliate programs in order support the site and to allow it to continue as a FREE service to you the users. These partners/advertisers are typically part of larger management services which use what are called Third-Party elements or cookies. The typical collection of data by these companies is anonymous, however if you are concerned, then by all means please feel free to investigate further. Below you will find a list of the management companies which you may encounter on NowInStock.net and links to their respective privacy information pages. 

**Viewing & Blocking Data Trackers** \- If you are interested in seeing what trackers are being used while using any website including NowInStock.net, then you should check out the really cool plug-in from [Ghostery.com](http://www.ghostery.com/). It has a lot of great features including blocking specific trackers and ads, however, **please keep in mind that blocking the trackers and ads can result in loss of commission on our end, which in turn can affect how long NowInStock.net remains a FREE service.** We've been free since 2005 and plan to keep it that way as long as possible.

### Use of Internet Protocol Address

We use your Internet protocol (IP) address for several reasons: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, to help identify you, and to gather broad geographic information.

### Use of Registration Information

Our site's registration area requires customers to supply contact information, such an e-mail address, and may ask for phone numbers or demographic information, such as your ZIP code. We use this information to send you promotional materials from our company. We NEVER share personal information with partners or third-parties. Users may opt out of, or opt in to our promotional e-mail messages at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.)

### Use of Demographic Information

We also collect demographic and profile data that we use to tailor your experience at NowInStock.net. Based on this information, we display products and content we feel you might interest you.

### Use of Order Information

NowInStock.net does not process orders. We only refer our users to retailers that collect information to process orders. We never collect ordering information of specific individuals from these retailers.

### Use of Online Survey Information

To participate in our online surveys, you will be required to supply contact and/or demographic information. NowInStock.net uses this data to send you information about the company. We might use this information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) 

### Use of Information Collected in Contests

To participate in our contests, you will be required to supply contact and demographic information. NowInStock.net uses this data to send you information about the company. We might use this information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Demographic and profile data are collected at our site and may be used to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel you would most interest you.

### Public Forums Guidelines

NowInStock.net offers chat rooms and bulletin boards. Please note that information that is disclosed in these arenas becomes public. Use caution in disclosing any personal information.

### Security

NowInStock.net takes every precaution to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information placed under our control. In the event of a breach of security, all parties will be notified. 

### Children's Guidelines

We do not collect or use any online contact information or identifiable off-line contact information about a child without parental consent. We do not distribute personally identifiable information about children without parental consent. We do not give children the ability to post or distribute personal information without prior consent. We do not entice children with games or contests that would encourage them to disclose personal information.

### Opt Out/Opt In

NowInStock.net allows users to opt out of receiving e-mails. To opt out of our mailings, each e-mail contains an "Unsubscribe" link. Use this link to a remove your e-mail from that given mailing list. Also, occasionally we send "Site" and "Product" Updates, you can opt out of these e-mails on your My Account page after logging into your account. Or you can also contact us directly via our contact form (See Contact Us, below.)

##### Data Removal

If you are a subscriber, having created an account with NowInStock.net, and want to delete all your information, simply request to delete your account from the [My Account](https://www.nowinstock.net/users/myAccount.php) page. All data will be deleted forever including any records of past actions such as opting-in to product updates or newsletters.

### Disclaimer

This site contains links to other sites. NowInStock.net is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites.
